http://www.boxrec.com/en/terms_conditions#cookies

Boxing's Official Record Keeper
sign up
|
login
all fighters doctor inspector judge manager matchmaker promoter referee supervisor event
BoxRec Terms and Conditions
By accessing "BoxRec" (hereinafter "we", "us", "our", "BoxRec", "http://boxrec.com", "The Publisher", "The Site"), you agree to be legally bound by the following terms.
If you do not agree to be legally bound by all of the following terms then please do not access and/or use "BoxRec".
We may change these at any time and we’ll do our utmost in informing you, though it would be prudent to review this regularly yourself as your continued usage of "BoxRec" after changes mean you agree to be legally bound by these terms as they are updated and/or amended.
By registering with BoxRec you are also registering to use the BoxRec forum. Our forums are powered by phpBB (hereinafter "they", "them", "their", "phpBB software", "www.phpbb.com", "phpBB Limited", "phpBB Teams") which is a bulletin board solution released under the "GNU General Public License v2" (hereinafter "GPL") and can be downloaded from www.phpbb.com. The phpBB software only facilitates internet based discussions; phpBB Limited is not responsible for what we allow and/or disallow as permissible content and/or conduct. For further information about phpBB, please see: https://www.phpbb.com/.
All copyright and other rights that subsist in the home page and in the sub-domain pages of BoxRec are owned by BoxRec.
The copyright, and other rights, in some of the material appearing on or in the Site may belong to a third party. It is your responsibility to obtain any licences or permissions that may be required to use such material and you agree to pay any costs or expenses incurred by the Publisher which arise as a result of your failure to obtain such licences and permissions.
If you would like to obtain permission for use of BoxRec content please Contact Us
The use of BoxRec ratings by media, betting or fantasy platforms requires an official licence. Please Contact Us with any queries. Any activity against this Article will be viewed as a direct violation of our policy.
Subject to what is said below, you may download, view, print, copy on the hard disk of your computer (but not photocopy) and use material on the Site for your own personal non-commercial purposes. You may not without the prior written agreement of the Publisher:
create a database (electronic or otherwise) containing material downloaded or otherwise obtained from the Site
redistribute, retransmit or re-circulate any material obtained from the Site to any third party
remove copyright or trade mark notices from any copies of any material made in accordance with these terms
Access to parts of the Site is restricted or password-protected. You may not download, view, print, use or otherwise seek to gain access to any material that is held in any parts of the Site that are restricted or password-protected unless you have proper authorisation or have been issued a valid password.
If you are a registered user or subscriber, you are not permitted to share your user name and password with anyone else. A password is for one person’s use. Sharing a password means a copy of our content may subsequently be made by someone who is not authorised to do so. Password sharing is a breach of our terms and conditions and is likely to result in an infringement of copyright. We monitor usage to detect password sharing.
The use of automated systems or software to extract data from boxrec.com (‘screen scraping’) is prohibited unless the third party has directly concluded a written licence agreement with BoxRec in which permits it access to BoxRec’s information.
You agree that you will not use BoxRec:
for the posting, uploading, e-mailing or other transmission of any material, the publication, dissemination, use or possession of which infringes the rights of any person or which is unlawful in any other respect
in any way which is abusive, defamatory, vulgar, slanderous, hateful, threatening, sexually-orientated or obscene or which will harass, distress or inconvenience any person or which may restrict or inhibit the use and enjoyment of the Site by any person
for the posting, uploading, or any other transmission of material that may violate any laws be it of your country, the country where "BoxRec" is hosted or International Law. Doing so may lead to you being immediately and permanently banned, with notification of your Internet Service Provider if deemed required by us. The IP address of all posts are recorded to aid in enforcing these conditions. You agree that "BoxRec" have the right to remove, edit, move or close any topic at any time should we see fit. As a user you agree to any information you have entered to being stored in a database. While this information will not be disclosed to any third party without your consent, neither "BoxRec" nor phpBB shall be held responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised
for the posting, uploading, e-mailing or other transmission of any unsolicited or unauthorised advertising, promotional materials, “junk mail”, “spam”, “chain letters”, “pyramid schemes” or any other form of solicitation or commercial exploitation
for the posting, uploading, e-mailing or other transmission of any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, restrict, destroy, limit the functionality of or compromise the integrity of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment
in any way that may bring the Publisher into disrepute
What information do we collect?
BoxRec collects information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.
When registering on BoxRec, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. Your privacy is a very sensitive subject for us and we take it very seriously.
Your account will at a bare minimum contain a uniquely identifiable name (hereinafter “your user name”), a personal password used for logging into your account (hereinafter “your password”) and a personal, valid e-mail address (hereinafter “your e-mail”). Your information for your account at BoxRec is protected by data-protection laws applicable in the country that hosts us. Any information beyond your user name, your password, and your e-mail address required by BoxRec during the registration process is either mandatory or optional, at the discretion of BoxRec. In all cases, you have the option of what information in your account is publicly displayed. Furthermore, within your account, you have the option to opt-in or opt-out of automatically generated e-mails from the phpBB software.
Your password is ciphered (a one-way hash) so that it is secure. However, it is recommended that you do not reuse the same password across a number of different websites. Your password is the means of accessing your account at BoxRec, so please guard it carefully and under no circumstance will anyone affiliated with BoxRec, BoxRec or another 3rd party, legitimately ask you for your password. Should you forget your password for your account, you can use the “I forgot my password” feature provided by the phpBB software. This process will ask you to submit your user name and your e-mail, then the phpBB software will generate a new password to reclaim your account.
BoxRec may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.
Should you purchase from our site we also record the payments details that are passed to us from the PayPal service.
We do not pass this information on.
We do not have access to credit card or bank account information.
What does BoxRec use your information for?
Any of the information BoxRec collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
To provide a service for you
To improve our website
To improve customer service
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
How does BoxRec protect your information?
BoxRec implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that a site can place on your computer or mobile device to store certain information. We use cookies to keep track of how you use our website, remember if you are logged in or not, make our website work efficiently, and deliver relevant content including advertisement. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to the site.
Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to BoxRec and/or other sites on the Internet.
You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads
You can set up your browser not to allow cookies, however some parts our site would not function properly. You can get more information about cookies here: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/
Partners
Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement.
For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. BoxRec.com have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Your Consent
To login to BoxRec or the Forum all users must consent to BoxRec to the storing of their login details and IP address as detailed in this page.
If no consent is given it will be prompted for when logging in.
Change Consent
Boxing Participants
BoxRec display information to the public pertaining to participants in the sport of Boxing, for example Boxers, Managers, Referee's etc.
The information for these participants is stored and processed under the Lawful Basis of Legitimate Interest.
Contact us
For any questions regarding the terms and conditions and your usage of BoxRec please send us an email
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on May 23rd, 2018.
©BoxRec : data may be incomplete/inaccurate
:
BoxRec.com uses cookies to make the site simpler.
